forangelsonly.org 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy - ForAngelsOnly.Org

**ForAngelsOnly.org:   Privacy Policy**

This statement covers the site www.ForAngelsOnly.org (ForAngelsOnly.org). Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access ForAngelsOnly.org. Your use of ForAngelsOnly.org indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

 **Information Collection**

ForAngelsOnly.org is the sole owner of the information collected on www.ForAngelsOnly.org. ForAngelsOnly.org may collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

 **Comments**

In order to enhance their use of this Web site, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must submit information including a valid email address. ForAngelsOnly.org uses this information to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use, and will not pass this information to any other organization.

 **Third Party Cookies**

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, ForAngelsOnly.org has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by ForAngelsOnly.org only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Third Party Advertising**

Adertuser delivers the advertisements appearing on ForAngelsOnly.org to users, among other services. Information about user’s visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

 **Log Files**

Like most standard Website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, ForAngelsOnly.org may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Website.

 **Business Transitions**

In the event ForAngelsOnly.org goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, user’s personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

 **Links**

ForAngelsOnly.org contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, ForAngelsOnly.org, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by ForAngelsOnly.org.

 **Notification of   Changes**

Whenever ForAngelsOnly.org changes our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at Admin at ForAngelsOnly.org.
